[
  {
    "Number": 1,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 10 mcg/min of a drug for 10 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 6,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 2,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 5 mcg/min of a drug for 3 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 0.9,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 3,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 40 mcg/min of a drug for 8 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 19.2,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 4,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 35 mcg/min of a drug for 5 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 10.5,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 5,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 35 mcg/min of a drug for 5 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 10.5,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 6,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 45 mcg/min of a drug for 10 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 27,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 7,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 20 mcg/min of a drug for 6 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 7.2,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 8,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 10 mcg/min of a drug for 10 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 6,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 9,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 35 mcg/min of a drug for 6 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 12.6,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 10,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 25 mcg/min of a drug for 11 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 16.5,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 11,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 10 mcg/min of a drug for 12 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 7.2,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 12,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 10 mcg/min of a drug for 10 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 6,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 13,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 35 mcg/min of a drug for 4 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 8.4,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 14,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 30 mcg/min of a drug for 11 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 19.8,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 15,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 5 mcg/min of a drug for 6 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 1.8,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 16,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 15 mcg/min of a drug for 8 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 7.2,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 17,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 5 mcg/min of a drug for 4 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 1.2,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 18,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 35 mcg/min of a drug for 12 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 25.2,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 19,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 30 mcg/min of a drug for 6 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 10.8,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 20,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 35 mcg/min of a drug for 6 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 12.6,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 21,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 15 mcg/min of a drug for 12 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 10.8,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 22,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 5 mcg/min of a drug for 10 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 3,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 23,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 50 mcg/min of a drug for 7 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 21,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 24,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 35 mcg/min of a drug for 7 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 14.7,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 25,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 15 mcg/min of a drug for 7 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 6.3,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 26,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 30 mcg/min of a drug for 9 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 16.2,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 27,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 45 mcg/min of a drug for 12 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 32.4,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 28,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 15 mcg/min of a drug for 7 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 6.3,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 29,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 35 mcg/min of a drug for 11 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 23.1,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 30,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 25 mcg/min of a drug for 11 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 16.5,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 31,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 45 mcg/min of a drug for 3 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 8.1,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 32,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 25 mcg/min of a drug for 8 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 12,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 33,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 15 mcg/min of a drug for 7 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 6.3,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 34,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 35 mcg/min of a drug for 3 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 6.3,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 35,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 15 mcg/min of a drug for 9 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 8.1,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 36,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 45 mcg/min of a drug for 10 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 27,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 37,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 5 mcg/min of a drug for 7 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 2.1,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 38,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 25 mcg/min of a drug for 5 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 7.5,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 39,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 45 mcg/min of a drug for 8 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 21.6,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 40,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 25 mcg/min of a drug for 12 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 18,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 41,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 25 mcg/min of a drug for 6 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 42,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 30 mcg/min of a drug for 5 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 43,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 20 mcg/min of a drug for 8 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 9.6,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 44,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 40 mcg/min of a drug for 2 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 4.8,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 45,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 50 mcg/min of a drug for 2 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 6,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 46,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 40 mcg/min of a drug for 7 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 16.8,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 47,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 5 mcg/min of a drug for 3 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 0.9,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 48,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 20 mcg/min of a drug for 7 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 8.4,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 49,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 25 mcg/min of a drug for 2 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 3,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 50,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 5 mcg/min of a drug for 8 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 2.4,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 51,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 40 mcg/min of a drug for 4 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 9.6,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 52,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 10 mcg/min of a drug for 2 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 1.2,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 53,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 5 mcg/min of a drug for 3 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 0.9,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 54,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 50 mcg/min of a drug for 11 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 33,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 55,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 35 mcg/min of a drug for 6 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 12.6,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 56,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 15 mcg/min of a drug for 7 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 6.3,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 57,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 20 mcg/min of a drug for 10 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 12,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 58,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 15 mcg/min of a drug for 6 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 5.4,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 59,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 20 mcg/min of a drug for 10 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 12,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 60,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 45 mcg/min of a drug for 2 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 5.4,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 61,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 50 mcg/min of a drug for 5 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 15,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 62,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 25 mcg/min of a drug for 7 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 10.5,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 63,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 45 mcg/min of a drug for 3 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 8.1,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 64,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 35 mcg/min of a drug for 3 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 6.3,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 65,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 45 mcg/min of a drug for 9 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 24.3,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 66,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 5 mcg/min of a drug for 2 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 0.6,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 67,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 5 mcg/min of a drug for 7 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 2.1,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 68,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 30 mcg/min of a drug for 5 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 69,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 35 mcg/min of a drug for 10 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 21,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 70,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 25 mcg/min of a drug for 4 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 6,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 71,
    "Question": "If a patient requires 50 mcg/min of a drug for 6 hours, what is the total amount of the drug they will require in milligrams?  Give your answer to <strong> 1 decimal place </strong>",
    "Answer": 18,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 72,
    "Question": "A 60 kg patient requires 58 mg/kg/minute for 10 minutes, delivered by a 12 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 290,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 73,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 28 mg/kg/minute for 45 minutes, delivered by a 22.5 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 280,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 74,
    "Question": "A 60 kg patient requires 28 mg/kg/minute for 45 minutes, delivered by a 27 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 280,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 75,
    "Question": "A 70 kg patient requires 64 mg/kg/minute for 15 minutes, delivered by a 21 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 320,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 76,
    "Question": "A 80 kg patient requires 78 mg/kg/minute for 15 minutes, delivered by a 24 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 390,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 77,
    "Question": "A 70 kg patient requires 66 mg/kg/minute for 40 minutes, delivered by a 84 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 220,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 78,
    "Question": "A 80 kg patient requires 74 mg/kg/minute for 10 minutes, delivered by a 16 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 370,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 79,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 30 mg/kg/minute for 35 minutes, delivered by a 17.5 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 300,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 80,
    "Question": "A 40 kg patient requires 68 mg/kg/minute for 30 minutes, delivered by a 24 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 340,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 81,
    "Question": "A 80 kg patient requires 37 mg/kg/minute for 35 minutes, delivered by a 28 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 370,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 82,
    "Question": "A 40 kg patient requires 36 mg/kg/minute for 30 minutes, delivered by a 12 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 360,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 83,
    "Question": "A 70 kg patient requires 27 mg/kg/minute for 15 minutes, delivered by a 10.5 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 270,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 84,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 48 mg/kg/minute for 5 minutes, delivered by a 5 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 240,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 85,
    "Question": "A 90 kg patient requires 81 mg/kg/minute for 10 minutes, delivered by a 27 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 270,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 86,
    "Question": "A 30 kg patient requires 31 mg/kg/minute for 35 minutes, delivered by a 10.5 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 310,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 87,
    "Question": "A 40 kg patient requires 30 mg/kg/minute for 5 minutes, delivered by a 2 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 300,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 88,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 64 mg/kg/minute for 40 minutes, delivered by a 40 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 320,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 89,
    "Question": "A 40 kg patient requires 68 mg/kg/minute for 30 minutes, delivered by a 24 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 340,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 90,
    "Question": "A 60 kg patient requires 30 mg/kg/minute for 5 minutes, delivered by a 3 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 300,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 91,
    "Question": "A 40 kg patient requires 38 mg/kg/minute for 35 minutes, delivered by a 14 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 380,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 92,
    "Question": "A 70 kg patient requires 72 mg/kg/minute for 30 minutes, delivered by a 63 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 240,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 93,
    "Question": "A 60 kg patient requires 44 mg/kg/minute for 20 minutes, delivered by a 24 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 220,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 94,
    "Question": "A 80 kg patient requires 30 mg/kg/minute for 20 minutes, delivered by a 16 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 300,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 95,
    "Question": "A 80 kg patient requires 34 mg/kg/minute for 40 minutes, delivered by a 32 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 340,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 96,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 44 mg/kg/minute for 35 minutes, delivered by a 35 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 220,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 97,
    "Question": "A 70 kg patient requires 20 mg/kg/minute for 5 minutes, delivered by a 3.5 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 98,
    "Question": "A 70 kg patient requires 35 mg/kg/minute for 10 minutes, delivered by a 7 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 350,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 99,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 38 mg/kg/minute for 10 minutes, delivered by a 5 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 380,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 100,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 63 mg/kg/minute for 45 minutes, delivered by a 67.5 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 210,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 101,
    "Question": "A 80 kg patient requires 50 mg/kg/minute for 30 minutes, delivered by a 48 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 250,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 102,
    "Question": "A 60 kg patient requires 36 mg/kg/minute for 25 minutes, delivered by a 15 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 360,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 103,
    "Question": "A 70 kg patient requires 40 mg/kg/minute for 10 minutes, delivered by a 7 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 400,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 104,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 38 mg/kg/minute for 35 minutes, delivered by a 17.5 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 380,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 105,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 35 mg/kg/minute for 40 minutes, delivered by a 20 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 350,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 106,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 87 mg/kg/minute for 35 minutes, delivered by a 52.5 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 290,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 107,
    "Question": "A 80 kg patient requires 62 mg/kg/minute for 30 minutes, delivered by a 48 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 310,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 108,
    "Question": "A 80 kg patient requires 60 mg/kg/minute for 5 minutes, delivered by a 12 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 109,
    "Question": "A 60 kg patient requires 69 mg/kg/minute for 45 minutes, delivered by a 81 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 230,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 110,
    "Question": "A 70 kg patient requires 52 mg/kg/minute for 25 minutes, delivered by a 35 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 260,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 111,
    "Question": "A 40 kg patient requires 38 mg/kg/minute for 30 minutes, delivered by a 12 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 380,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 112,
    "Question": "A 90 kg patient requires 80 mg/kg/minute for 15 minutes, delivered by a 54 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 113,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 66 mg/kg/minute for 15 minutes, delivered by a 22.5 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 220,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 114,
    "Question": "A 70 kg patient requires 48 mg/kg/minute for 25 minutes, delivered by a 35 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 240,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 115,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 37 mg/kg/minute for 45 minutes, delivered by a 22.5 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 370,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 116,
    "Question": "A 60 kg patient requires 72 mg/kg/minute for 10 minutes, delivered by a 18 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 240,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 117,
    "Question": "A 90 kg patient requires 44 mg/kg/minute for 35 minutes, delivered by a 63 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 220,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 118,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 56 mg/kg/minute for 20 minutes, delivered by a 20 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 280,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 119,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 27 mg/kg/minute for 40 minutes, delivered by a 20 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 270,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 120,
    "Question": "A 30 kg patient requires 56 mg/kg/minute for 40 minutes, delivered by a 24 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 280,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 121,
    "Question": "A 40 kg patient requires 31 mg/kg/minute for 40 minutes, delivered by a 16 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 310,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 122,
    "Question": "A 80 kg patient requires 60 mg/kg/minute for 10 minutes, delivered by a 24 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 123,
    "Question": "A 60 kg patient requires 70 mg/kg/minute for 5 minutes, delivered by a 6 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 350,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 124,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 44 mg/kg/minute for 10 minutes, delivered by a 10 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 220,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 125,
    "Question": "A 80 kg patient requires 54 mg/kg/minute for 40 minutes, delivered by a 64 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 270,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 126,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 27 mg/kg/minute for 30 minutes, delivered by a 15 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 270,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 127,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 48 mg/kg/minute for 15 minutes, delivered by a 15 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 240,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 128,
    "Question": "A 90 kg patient requires 58 mg/kg/minute for 40 minutes, delivered by a 72 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 290,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 129,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 64 mg/kg/minute for 35 minutes, delivered by a 35 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 320,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 130,
    "Question": "A 60 kg patient requires 76 mg/kg/minute for 10 minutes, delivered by a 12 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 380,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 131,
    "Question": "A 80 kg patient requires 31 mg/kg/minute for 10 minutes, delivered by a 8 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 310,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 132,
    "Question": "A 80 kg patient requires 37 mg/kg/minute for 45 minutes, delivered by a 36 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 370,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 133,
    "Question": "A 80 kg patient requires 40 mg/kg/minute for 20 minutes, delivered by a 32 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 134,
    "Question": "A 60 kg patient requires 76 mg/kg/minute for 10 minutes, delivered by a 12 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 380,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 135,
    "Question": "A 70 kg patient requires 68 mg/kg/minute for 20 minutes, delivered by a 28 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 340,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 136,
    "Question": "A 40 kg patient requires 34 mg/kg/minute for 5 minutes, delivered by a 2 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 340,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 137,
    "Question": "A 90 kg patient requires 66 mg/kg/minute for 30 minutes, delivered by a 81 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 220,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 138,
    "Question": "A 30 kg patient requires 58 mg/kg/minute for 40 minutes, delivered by a 24 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 290,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 139,
    "Question": "A 70 kg patient requires 64 mg/kg/minute for 45 minutes, delivered by a 63 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 320,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 140,
    "Question": "A 50 kg patient requires 54 mg/kg/minute for 5 minutes, delivered by a 5 %w/v solution. How much solution will they need in ml?",
    "Answer": 270,
    "Units": "ml"
  }
]
